

- Phone: +94 717644732
- sinethedirisinghe123@gmail.com
- LinkedIn
- Bē Portfolio
- 33/8, Weerangula, Yakkala

Personal

Date of Brith : 04 Nov 2000

♦ Gender : Male

Nationality : Sri Lankan

Languages : Sinhala, English

Skills

- Wireframing ◆ Prototyping
- UI designUser testing
- UX designUsability Research

Tools

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe PS
- Illustrator









SINETH EDIRISINGHE

Associate UI/UX Designer @

About me

I'm a passionate UI UX designer with a mission to transform ideas into visually stunning and user-friendly experiences. With 3 years in the design industry, I've had the pleasure of collaborating with clients globally, turning concepts into reality.

Experiences

Supervisor - UI/UX Designer

Viso Labs (PVT) Ltd

Part Time - UI/UX Designer Aug 2023 - Present

Logiccodex solutions (PVT) Ltd

Mentor - UI/UX Designer Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Future Xplora Academy

Associate - UI/UX Designer Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

Viso Labs (PVT) Ltd

Internship - UI/UX Designer April 2023 - Jun 2023

Viso Labs (PVT) Ltd

Education

Undergraduate

SLTC Research University

B.Sc.(Hons) in Information Technology specialized in Cyber Security

GCE Advanced Level

2019

Feb 2020 - Present

Jan 2024 - Present

Bandaranayake Collage Gampaha

Technology stream

Courses

Foundation of user experience(UX) design course in Coursera

UI/UX design course in FSD Academy

Cyber security and networking course on NextGen Campus

Cyber security course in CYBERHAT 1.0 online workshop

Cloud computing application, part 01: cloud system and infrastructure in Coursera

IoT(Internet of Things) wireless & cloud computing emerging technologies in Coursera

References

Dr. Yohan Pandigama Founder-C2L3 Lecture(CS) - Sri Lanka Technological Campus, Padukka. Fomer HoD-IT - CINEC Campus, Malabe. MIEEE, MIEEE-CS, MACM, MBCS, MSC(SL), MSC, BIT 0713008883 yohanp@sltc.ac.lk Dr. Dileepa Fernando Post doctoral Research Fellow- HP-NTU Corporate Lab, Singapore. dileepa.fernando@ntu.edu.sg